One of the great successes of the Republican Party in recent decades is the relentless propagation of a simple formula for economic growth: tax cuts.
近几十年来，共和党取得的一大成功，就是不遗余力地宣扬一个促进经济增长的简单公式：减税。
The formula doesn’t work, but that has not affected its popularity.
这个公式并不奏效，但这并没有影响它受欢迎的程度。
And while the cult of tax cuts has attracted many critics, it lacks for obvious rivals.
而且，尽管减税崇拜招来了许多批评者，它却缺少明显的竞争对手。
Democratic politicians have tended to campaign on helping people left behind by economic growth.
民主党政客往往把帮助那些被经济增长甩在后面的人作为竞选主张。
When Democrats do talk about encouraging economic growth, they often sound like Republicans.
民主党人真的谈到促进经济增长时，听起来往往像共和党人。
This is not just a political problem for Democrats; it is an economic problem for the United States.
这不只是民主党人面临的政治问题，也是美国面临的经济问题。
The nation needs a better story about the drivers of economic growth.
关于经济增长的驱动因素，这个国家需要一套更好的说法。
The painful lessons of recent decades point to a promising candidate: higher wages.
近几十年来的惨痛教训指向一个有希望的候选答案：提高工资。
Raising the wages of American workers ought to be the priority of economic policymakers.
提高美国工人的工资应该成为经济政策制定者的首要任务。
We’d all be better off paying less attention to quarterly updates on the growth of the nation’s gross domestic product (GDP) and focusing instead on the growth of workers’ paychecks.
我们大家最好少关注每季度发布的本国国内生产总值（GDP）增长数据，转而关注工人薪水的增长。
Set aside, for the moment, the familiar argument for higher wages: fairness.
暂且撇开支持提高工资的那个常见理由：公平。
The argument here is that higher wages can fuel the engine of economic growth.
这里要提出的论点是，提高工资能够为经济增长的引擎提供动力。
Perhaps the most famous illustration of the benefits is the story of Henry Ford’s decision in 1914 to pay $5 a day to workers on his Model T assembly lines.
要说明提高工资的好处，最著名的例证或许就是亨利·福特的故事：1914年，他决定给自己T型车装配线上的工人每天发5美元工资。
He did it to increase production—he was paying a premium to maintain a reliable workforce.
他这样做是为了提高产量——他支付额外报酬，是为了保持一支可靠的劳动力队伍。
The unexpected benefit was that Ford’s factory workers became Ford customers, too.
意想不到的好处是，福特的工厂工人也成了福特的顾客。
The same logic still holds: Consumption drives the American economy, and workers who are paid more can spend more.
同样的逻辑如今依然成立：消费推动着美国经济，而工资更高的工人能花更多的钱。
Mainstream economists insist that it is impossible to order up a sustainable increase in wages because compensation levels reflect the unerring judgment of market forces.
主流经济学家坚称，不可能一声令下就让工资实现可持续增长，因为薪酬水平反映的是市场力量准确无误的判断。
The conventional wisdom held that productivity growth was the only route to higher wages.
传统观点认为，生产率增长是通往更高工资的唯一途径。
Through that lens, efforts to negotiate higher wages were counterproductive.
从这个角度看，通过谈判争取更高工资的努力是适得其反的。
Minimum-wage laws would raise unemployment because there was only so much money in the wage pool, and if some people got more, others would get none.
按照这种观点，最低工资法会推高失业率，因为工资池里的钱就那么多，如果一些人拿得多了，另一些人就会什么也拿不到。
It was in the context of this worldview that it became popular to argue that tax cuts would drive prosperity.
正是在这种世界观的背景下，主张减税会推动繁荣的论调开始流行起来。
Rich people would invest, productivity would increase, wages would rise.
富人会投资，生产率会提高，工资会上涨。
In the real world, things are more complicated.
在现实世界中，情况更为复杂。
Wages are influenced by a tug of war between employers and workers, and employers have been winning.
工资受雇主和工人之间拉锯战的影响，而雇主一直占上风。
One clear piece of evidence is the widening gap between productivity growth and wage growth since roughly 1970.
一个明显的证据是，大约自1970年以来，生产率增长与工资增长之间的差距不断扩大。
Productivity has more than doubled; wages have lagged far behind.
生产率已经翻了一番还多，而工资远远落后。
A focus on wage growth would provide an antidote to the attractive simplicity of the belief in the magical power of tax cuts.
相信减税具有神奇力量，这种信念简单得诱人，而关注工资增长将提供一剂解药，化解这种诱惑。